Jung, Cheyoon

Date of birth: 05 Dec 1994
Mobile: +36 30 856 1241
Email: jessietwo94@gmail.com
Website: www.jcheyoon.com
Github: github.com/JCheyoon

I majored **Movie Image Design** and worked as a graphic designer for almost 2 years, where I learned to use several design tools. I also got introduced to **the world of IT** and later started to study about software development.

I would like to get more familiar with this industry and work in an atmosphere where I can feel **motivated**.

Keeping up my **professional development** is important for me, while I support my team using the **experiences and soft skills** I brought from my prior positions.

Working experience

Designer, MOON42 RDI Ltd.

Oct 2020 - Sep 2021, Budapest, Hungary

Making animations for promotional videos using After Effects. Drawing vector illustrations using Illustrator.

Data Coordinator, Tumlare Corportation

Sep 2018 - Oct 2020, Budapest, Hungary

Handling Hotel contracts data. Keeping contact with suppliers and satellite offices.

Designer, Fairip

Aug 2017 - Jun 2018, Seoul, Korea

Making animations for promotional videos using After Effects. Taking and Editing videos. Supporting Marketing Management.

Strengths

- Open, expressive personality, usually feel easy to adapt to new environments and tasks
- Single-focus thinking style, but still like to think in high context and see the big picture
- Routine Persistence, Adaptable to tasks requiring repetition, maintaining a commitment to excellence

What I would like to learn, improve

Software development lifecycle, process



Skills

Main stack:

- > REACT
- > JAVASCRIPT
- > TYPESCRIPT

Tech I also use every day:

- > HTML5
- > CSS3 / SCSS
- > GIT
- > REST APIs

I'm also familiar with:

ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS | ILLUSTRATOR | PHOTOSHOP | PREMIERE | CINEMA4D | GITHUB | React Three Fiber

Education

Self-learning

2021 - Present, Various online courses and tutorials of programming and web development

Tower Nyelviskola, Hungary

Jun 2018 - Aug 2018, English learning

Baguio English Communication Institute, Philippines

Feb 2016 - Jul 2016, English learing

Hyanyang Women University, Seoul

2013-2015, Movie Image Design

Previous Working experiences

Design Assistant, Harmony Interior Oct 2015 - Jul 2017, Seoul, Korea

Part-timer, Korea Racing Authority (Part-time) Aug 2015 - Jan 2016, Seoul, Korea

Video Editor, SK C&C (Part-time) Jul 2015 - Aug 2015, Gwangju, Korea

Licenses & Certifications

Craftsman Computer Graphics Operation

Issued Apr 2017, HRD Korea (Credential ID 17401021654T)

Industrial Engineer Colorist

Issued Nov 2014 HRD Korea (Credential ID 14203021293H)

Graphic Technology Qualification

Issued Jul 2014 KPC (GA01G14106240150)

Languages

Korean

Native language

English

Fluent oral and written skills

Hungarian

Basic level

Hobbies, Range of interests

- Yoga
- Traveling
- Watching TV-shows (sci-fi, fantasy, documentaries)
- Cooking
- Photography, photo editing